Ihor Muliar

Data Scientist

+38 093 31 17 866 ihor.muliar22@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/ihor-muliar github.com/lhorMuliar

Junior data scientist with 1+ years of experience in project work and freelance jobs. Seeking a data science job. Skilled in machine learning, statistics, problem solving, and programming.

Experience

Freelance Data Scientist

2020-2021

Upwork:

 Used an ensemble machine-learning algorithm to predict the percentage of opening bank account

Kaggle:

- Risk analysis
- Fraud detection
- Customer segmentation
- Census income analysis
- Churn prediction
- Price prediction

TV broadcasting engineer

First Business Television Channel

Mar 2018 - Sep 2018

- Hardware studio work, preparation and broadcasting of TV broadcasts
- Recording of TV programs in the studio and their subsequent editing and uploading to the database.
- Elimination of breakdowns and defects in the work of hardware and studio equipment.
- Recording on the video server of TV programs.

Education

Taras Shevchenko National University of Kyiv

Bachelor of Computer Networking Systems and Telecommunications

Expected Graduation in 2024

Lyceum KPI

2009 - 2020

IT Step Academy

2015 - 2020

Skills

Hard skills:

- Python (Pandas, NumPy, Scikit-learn, Matplotlib, Seaborn, Pyplot, TenserFlow, Keras, OpenCv)
- Data Visualization
- Data Wrangling
- Data Management
- SQL
- Machine Learning / Deep Learning
- Microsoft Excel
- Probability & Statistics
- Multivariate Calculus & Linear Algebra

Soft skills:

- Problem-solving
- Understanding of technical documentation
- Communication and presentation
- Creativity

Languages:

- English (Upper-intermediate, FCE)
- Ukrainian (Native or bilingual proficiency)
- Russian (Native or bilingual proficiency)